# Eric Ma Chun Kit (馬俊傑)

Address: Mobile 96533432

Telephone: 31249317

Email: <a href="mailto:ericma@mac.com">ericma@mac.com</a>

# **Career Objective**

I am keen to utilize my selling and customer service skills in a representative role that focuses on building relationships with customers and Channels, as well as translation opportunities into new accounts.

# **Skills and Working Experiences**

Project Management Skill

In current Roles, I had been responsible to manage Wynn Palace / Macau Security and surveillance network implementation project, this project had been taken for almost 2 years, with spending 7 Million US dollars. This project included design, proof of concept, delivery, installation, implementation and maintenance phase. This project is still going forward. The experience that from this project had equipped difference management skill, including but not limited to communication, reporting, design, executing and monitoring.

Besides, I also response developing strategies and operating Mega Legend (Macau) Ltd. In this job rules, I'm not only need to find the new opportunities and also I need to grow up Mega Legend to become an essential, professional service partner in Macau. Up to now, we are now certified Cisco, Fortinet and Ruckus service partner in Macau Territory

#### Selling skills

In previous Roles, I have been responsible for developing strategies and identifying new opportunities to turn these into reality. I understand the importance of their needs being identified, turning the products features into customer benefits and closing the deal that benefits both company and customer.

## Highly motivated

I have won major deals in previous positions and look forward to the opportunity to do the same thing for my career development. I establish goals for myself professionally and personally and then set about to achieve these as quickly as possible. Promotions in previous positions have been the result of these efforts being recognized and rewarded.

## *Knowledge of the IT industry*

I have worked in the IT industry for all of my working life, starting at the bottom as a sale executive, moving to up to corporate role as Sales and Account Manager. In my role, I need to handle both SME and business corporate accounts with various solutions to fulfill customer needs. My unique grounding enables me to fully understand the day to day operation of sales activities as well as its management.

#### Education

Tertiary	
2016	Cisco Certificate Network Associate (Router and Switch)
2015	Project Management Professional
2005-2008	Master of Information System
	The Hong Kong Polytechnic University
1996-1999	Bachelor of China Studies (Major Economics)
	Hong Kong Baptist University
1996	A Level, Immaculate Heart of Mary College
	Use of English, Chinese Language and Culture, History,
	Economics, Geography and Computer Application
1994	Cert Level, Immaculate Heart of Mary College
	English, Chinese, Maths, Economics, Geography, Computer,
	History, RS.

## **Employment History**

Sep 2014 – onward Territory Manager, Mega Legend (Asia) Ltd; Mega Legend (Macau) Ltd.

Develop the business in Macau Territory and manage major projects in Hong Kong and Macau

- Response the Project Management of Wynn Palace & Wynn Macau, Security and Surveillance Network, which project scale was up to 7 Million US dollars with using over 2 years to develop
- Response the business develop of Mega Legend (Macau) Ltd, Sales Revenue has increased almost five time, which achieve to 4 Million, start from 2014 to 2017

Jan 2008 – Aug 2014 Senior Product Manager, Ingram Micro (China) Ltd.

Maintain existing customers to achieve Sales Target. Introduced IBM and Symantec enterprise solution to support Channel Sales Growth

- Response the Business development of IBM Server, Symantec Anti Virus and backup software
- Successful to bring the Symantec and IBM revenue to grow nearly 20% in half year.
- Response the Business development of Cisco Product line and successful to bring the Cisco revenue to growth 3 times, which up to 28 Million US dollar from 2009 to 2014

Oct 2005 –Jan 2008 Account Manager, Assistant Sales Manager, Chevalier (Network Solutions) Ltd.

Maintain existing customers to achieve Sales Target. Introduced a gateway and enterprise solution to support Customer IT infrastructure growth.

- Implement email gateway system solution for one SME Account with over 1 millions.
- Successful negotiation of HP Storage and SAN Solution for customers with over 1.8 millions

May 2005 – Oct 2005 Sales Manager, Professional Computer Services Ltd. *Responsibilities* 

Identify new business opportunities and maintain existing customers to achieve Sales Target. Introduced a quotation and purchasing system to support sales activities and customer service.

#### Achievements

- Successful negotiation of sales contacts with Customers with over 2 million
- Implement quotation and Sales application increasing efficiency for Sales activities

2002 – May 2005 Account Manager, Senco-Masslink Technology Ltd. *Responsibilities* 

Prepare, design and propose any system planning or solutions to customer for their business need. Discover new business opportunities and maintain existing customers to enhance business grow. Lead a sales team to achieve sales goals.

#### Achievements

Successful negotiation of IBM Computer Supply contract of Hong Kong

- Productivity Council which over 3 millions for 1 year
- ➤ Implement one digital image solution for one wedding service company with over 1.5 million.
- ➤ Implement one backup system solution for SME Accounts with over 1.3 millions.
- ➤ Successful negotiation of IBM Computer Supply contract of Po Leung Kuk which over 1 million

2000 - 2002	Senior Account Executive, Senco-Masslink Technology Ltd.
1999 - 2000	Sales Executive, Senco-Masslink Technology Ltd.
1997 – 1998	Part Time Marketing Clerk, New World Telephone Ltd.